https://ciscobrewers.com/privacy-policy?privacy=false

Delivery
PRIVACY POLICYThis is a website of Craft Brew Alliance, and Cisco Brewers. Our postal address is929 N Russell StPortland, OR 97227
Craft Brew Alliance can be reached via e-mail at webmail@craftbrew.com
or you can reach us by telephone at 503-281-2437
USE OF INFORMATION PROVIDED TO CISCO BREWERS At Cisco Brewers, we are dedicated to respecting your privacy. We have therefore created the following privacy guidelines to protect your personal information. At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide this information to us voluntarily and knowingly. Accordingly, you do not have to sign-in to look at our site. However, if you specifically provide us with identifiable information, such as by asking to be placed on a mailing list, or ordering items on our store front, we may periodically contact you. If you would like to contact Cisco Brewers without submitting personally identifiable information online, you can call us at (503) 281-2437. This policy may be revised without notice and you should read it whenever visiting this site.
COOKIES: Cisco Brewers uses “cookies” on this website. A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser, which is standard technology in the Internet world. When you access this site, the cookie indicates to us whether you have visited this site before or are a new visitor. The cookie does not acquire any personal information about you or provide us with any means to contact you. Further, the cookie does not extract any information from your computer. We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.
SECURITY: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server.
CLICKSTREAM DATA We collect click-stream data and HTTP protocol elements through access logs. This information is not personally identifiable and is used for Web site and system administration including: research and development, user analysis and business decision-making.
SURVEYS AND CONTESTS Our site may include surveys, notices of contests, or other promotions we are conducting. In some cases, these promotions will allow you to send your entry electronically. In such instances, we will describe the purpose for collecting such information and use the information you provide solely for the purpose of conducting the promotion.
When you make a reservation, we collect your name, contact information, driver’s license, credit card information, as well as information about your current reservation and we keep information on your reservation history.
This information is used by us and/or our agents: to support your interaction with our site, to deliver your purchases and to contact you again about other services and products we offer. We DO NOT share your name or contact information (including e-mail, telephone and physical address) with other companies. Cisco Brewers will not contact you except in a customer service capacity as a result of information you provided on this site.
FOR WEB SITE VISITORS WHO DO NOT MAKE PURCHASES OR OTHERWISE IDENTIFY THEMSELVES… If you do not sign on to our Web site, our Web server does not have access to personally identifiable information about you. It does not know your e-mail address unless you volunteer it. Cisco Brewers will not contact you except in a customer service capacity as a result of information you provided on this site.
CONDITIONS OF USE This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions of this site.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
Nantucket:Tel: 508-325-5929 | 5 Bartlett Farm Rd, Nantucket, MA 02554Boston:65 Northern Ave, Boston, MA 02210Portsmouth:Tel: 603-380-7575 | 35 Corporate Dr, Portsmouth, NH 03801
Contact
Are you 21+?
I am 21 years of age or older
I am under 21 years of age
By proceeding, you are confirming that you are 21+ and agree to our site’s privacy policy, and use of cookies. This site may use third party cookies to improve your browsing experience and marketing content.
